

JUNIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER
AND TRAINEE

Details

Poland +48729668414 rohzxz@gmail.com

Skills

JavaScript Es6+

React

HTML5

CSS3

Git

GitHub

tailwind css

nextjs

typescript

Critical thinking and problem solving

Links

portfolio

<u>linkedin</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

Hobbies

Communicating with people and love to discuss their ideas.
and Listening music

Languages

English

Profile

Computer software student who's always eager to learn modern technologies. Familiar with Programming languages, database systems, electronics, and networking. Have self-research on some popular tools and frameworks used in IT markets. I have lived in Poland last two years. right now I am learning core JavaScript and full stack development path. I am a quick learner... I like to learn new things. and I m fascinated by this industry.

Employment History

Non-Commercial experience:

2022 - 2023

- Tesla simple clone website using React fully responsive.
- good knowledge of fetching data from the API.
- · currently, I'm working on a website using CRUD system.
- basic knowledge version control system(git)
- ability to solve the problem.
- taking responsibility for my code.
- · Constantly learning and improving.
- I made my portfolio using Next js. still improving when I need it.

Technician Assist, stog.sp zoo, poland

DECEMBER 2021 - JULY 2022

Analysis of PCB motherboard, Add and Update Software. Creating, maintaining, and entering information into databases.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science, degree , Maharshi Dayanand Sarswati University Ajmer,india

OCTOBER 2015 - JULY 2017

The full form of BCA is a bachelor's in Computer Application. BCA is a 3-year undergraduate degree program that focuses on knowledge of the basics of computer application and software development.

hospitality and management, SDH INSTITUTE, Singapore, Singapore

DECEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2021

skills and knowledge in people management, service delivery, leadership, finance, and marketing, as well as identifying, understanding, and responding to the needs of clients.

Courses

HTML5, CCS3, javascript, React, web development bootcamp., Udemy E-learning

OCTOBER 2022 - MARCH 2024

front end developer Path.., scrimba E-Learning bootcamp

JANUARY 2023 - APRIL 2023

working status

NOTE. Poland

I have a work permit in Poland and I am ready to relocate.